Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
(HUMMING TUNE)
(GRUNTS AND GASPS)
Illumination! Illumination!
(SQUEALING)
(SEAGULLS CALLING)
MAX: I've lived in this city all my life.
I'm Max.
And I'm the luckiest dog in New York
- because of her.
- (BARKING)
That's Katie.
Katie and I...
Well, we have the perfect relationship.
We met a few years ago.
And, boy, let me tell ya,
- we got along right away.
- (WHINING)
It was one of those relationships
- where you just know.
- (LAUGHS)
(TOY SQUEAKS)
And get this!
She was looking for a roommate.
And so was I!
So I just moved in that same day.
- (PANTING)
- It was perfect.
- (BARKING)
- We've been together ever since.
Katie would do anything for me.
- (PIGEON COOING)
- And I'm her loyal protector.
(BARKING)
- (SQUAWKS)
- (WHINING)
(LAUGHING)
MAX: Our love is...
How do I put this? (STUTTERING)
Our love is stronger than words.
Or shoes.
It's me and Katie.
- (PANTING)
- Katie and me.
Us against the world.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
- (LAUGHING)
- (BARKING)
I wouldn't go so far as
to call us soul mates,
even though any sane person
who saw us would.
(CHUCKLES)
There's just one little problem.
- (GROWLING SOFTLY)
- Pretty much every day...
Come on, Max.
...she leaves.
I'll see you tonight.
MAX: Sometimes I try stuff
to get her to stay.
Okay.
Sit.
Spin.
- Speak.
- (BARKS)
(LAUGHS) Okay. That's a good boy.
MAX: But it never works.
Where is she going?
(BARKING)
What could she possibly be doing?
(SIGHS)
Oh, I miss her so much.
- (KEYS JINGLING)
- (GASPS)
(STUTTERING) Oh my! She's back!
- (BARKING)
- Forgot my phone.
What took so long? Why did you...
Oh, come on!
Oh!
I miss her so much.
WOMAN 1: Bye, Gidget. Be a good doggy.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(SMACKING LIPS)
(GRUNTING)
Hey, Max.
Hey, Gidget.
Any plans today?
Uh, yes.
Big, big stuff today,
Gidget. I got big plans.
I'm gonna sit here, and I'm gonna
wait for Katie to come back.
Oh, that sounds exciting.
Well, I won't interrupt.
I've got a very busy day, too. (CHUCKLES)
(SIGHS)
WOMAN: Here you go. See you later, Chloe.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(CLATTERING)
(BARKING)
MAN 1: Bye, Peppy.
- (URINATING)
- (SIGHS)
MAN 2: So long, Mel.
- (TWEETING)
- MAN 3: Bye, Sweetpea.
See you, Gino.
- Bye, Mr. Wiggles.
- So long, pal.
- GIRL: I'll miss you, Shelly!
- MAN 4: Later, Runty.
WOMAN 3: Bye, everyone.
WOMAN 4: Bye.
(TWITTERING)
(GASPS)
(SIGHS)
(GROANING)
Mmm. (GROANING)
(WHIMPERS)
(GROANS)
(YELLS)
(GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
(BARKING)
(CLATTERING)
(GROANS)
(HOWLS SOFTLY)
(CLATTERING)
(GROANS)
(MEOWS)
(THUDDING)
- MAN: You be a good boy, Leonard.
- (CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(HEAVY METAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC CONTINUES PLAYING DISTANTLY)
- (MEOWS)
- (THUDDING)
Hey, Max.
Hey, Chloe, do you ever wonder
where they go during the day?
Do you know what? I just...
I don't really care. (GRUNTS)
Maybe that's what it's like for you,
but Katie and I have
a different relationship.
You're a cat. So maybe that's why.
Because nobody could ever love
a cat the way they love a dog.
I'm just saying. Maybe that's why.
Whatever you need to tell yourself.
(GRUNTS AND SCREAMS)
- (PURRS)
- (SWEETPEA TWITTERING)